

# **MAULANA MALIK IBRAHIM**

Bondowoso, East Java (68219) • mmalikibrahim666@gmail.com https://linkedin.com/in/maulana-malik-ibrahim-7b4539216 https://github.com/LuciferLovesMe

# **SUMMARY**

I am an undergraduate student at State Polytechnic of Jember with a strong passion for software development. I specialize in web development using Next.js, Laravel, ASP.NET, and Express.js, and I am also interested in Android and desktop application development. I enjoy exploring new technologies and continuously improving my skills in these areas.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Intern, BRIN & Datains (Remote)

Aug 2024 - Dec 2024

Assisted in the development of web applications using the Next.js

# Web Engineer, PT Barouk Raya Teknologi (Remote)

Oct 2022 - Apr 2024

- Helping companies to create softwares for Bank BPR UMKM Jawa Timur
- Collaborated with frontend developers to integrate user-facing elements with server-side logic, ensuring seamless user experiences.
- Designed and implemented RESTful APIs using Laravel, enhancing system integration and data exchange for client applications.

# Intern Web Engineer, JV Partner Indonesia (Malang)

Jan 2021 - Apr 2021

- Assisted in the development of web applications using the Laravel framework, contributing to project features and enhancements.
- Participated in code review sessions, providing feedback and suggestions for optimizing code quality and performance.

#### **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelor of Informatics Engineering**

Aug 2022 - Present

State Polytechnic of Jember

- Explored the principles of software engineering, including software lifecycle, testing techniques, machine and quality assurance methodologies.
- Investigated web development technologies, including some Framewroks, to create responsive and user-friendly interfaces.

# **Software Engineering**

Aug 2019 - Jun 2022

State Vocational High School 1 of Bondowoso

- Gained expertise in object-oriented programming and design patterns to optimize code maintainability and scalability.
- Learned database design and management using SQL to create efficient data storage solutions for software applications.

#### **ACHIEVEMENT**

- Second Place at Lomba Kompetensi Siswa (LKS) SMK 2022 Tingkat Provinsi Jawa Timur in IT Software Solutions for Business
- Third Place at Lomba Kompetensi Siswa (LKS) SMK 2022 Tingkat Wilayah Kerja 2 Provinsi Jawa Timur in IT Software Solutions for Business

# **PROJECT**

- BelajarAksara, a mobile based app for learning Aksara Jawa for children
- Human Capital System, a web based app for Human Resource Management Sytem at Bank BPR UMKM Jawa Timur
- Loan Organization System, a web based app for organizing customer loans at Bank BPR UMKM Jawa Timur
- **Ketosin**, a mobile and web based app for Chairman of intra-school student organizations election at SMKN 1 Bondowoso
- **TukangIndonesia**, a web based app for booking a handyman onlinely at JV Partner Indonesia
- ActGrow, a web based app for connecting farmers and certification institutions